Guide to the Native American subject vertical file [ca.1850-2000.]
Native American subject vertical file
- Southwest - Indians - Art (Box 117)
- Speakers (Box 117)
- Spindle Whorls (Box 117)
- Spiritual Elders (Box 131)
  Wisdomkeepers calendar
- Spokane (Box 117)
- Sports (Box 117)
- Stamps and Coins (Box 117)
- Statues (Box 117)
- Steelworkers (Box 117)
- Stereotypes 1 (Box 117)
- Stereotypes 2 (Box 117)
- Sterilization (Box 117)
- Stockbridge Indians (Box 117)
- Stones and Stonework (Box 118)
- Substance abuse (Box 118)
- Surgery, Primitive (Box 118)
- Sweat Lodge (Box 118)
- Sycuan Indians (Box 118)
- Symbolism (Box 118)
- Symbolism - General and Correspondence (Box 118)
- Symbolism - Eastern (Box 118)
- Symbolism - Plains (Box 118)
- Symbolism - Western (Box 118)
- Tahltan Indians (Box 118)
- Taino Indians (Box 118)
- Tairona Indians (Box 118)
- Takelma Indians (Box 118)
- Talamonica Indians (Box 118)
- Tanning (Box 118)
- Tapiete Indians (Box 118)
- Tarahumara Indians (Box 118)
- Tarasco Indians (Box 118)
- Taxation (Box 118)
- Tehuelcha Indians (Box 119)
- Television - Indian Audience (Box 119)
- Tennessee - Antiquities (Box 119)
- Tennessee - Antiquities 2 (Box 119)
- Tennessee - History (Box 119)
- Tennessee - Indians (Box 119)
- Teotihuac'an (Box 119)
- Tepehuan Indians, Tepecano (Box 119)
- Termination (Box 119)
- Terreba Indians (Box 119)
- Tetes de Boule Indians (Box 119)
- Texas (Box 119)
- Texas - Antiquities 1 (Box 119)
- Texas - Antiquities 2 (Box 119)
- Texas - Bibliography (Box 119)
- Texas - History (Box 119)
- Texas - Indians (Box 119)
- Textiles (Box 119)
- Thanksgiving (Box 119)
- Theater (Box 119)
- Thunderbird (Box 119)
- Tierra del Fuego Indians (Box 120)
- Tillamook Indians (Box 120)
- Tinne Indians (Box 120)
- Tipis (Box 133)
- Tlingit Indians (Box 120)
- Toba Indians (Box 120)
- Tobacco and pipes 1 (Box 120)
- Tobacco and pipes 2 (Box 120)
- Tobacco and pipes 3 (Box 120)
- Tohono O'odham Indians (Box 120)
- Tohono O'odham Indians - Ethnology (Box 120)
- Tohono O'odham Indians - Legal Articles (Box 120)
- Tolowa Indians (Box 120)
- Toltecs (Box 120)
- Torture (Box 120)
- Totemism and totem poles 1 (Box 120)
- Totemism and totem poles 2 (Box 121)
- Touring Indian Country (Box 133)
  Computer game
- Tourism - Indian Business (Box 121)
- Tourist Art (Box 121)
- Trade (Box 121)
- Trade - Primitive (Box 121)
- Trade - Silver 1 (Box 121)
- Trade - Silver 2 (Box 121)
- Trading posts and Indian Traders (see also Military and Trading Posts) (Box 121)
- Trails - Oregon trails (Box 121)
- Trails - Santa Fe (Box 121)
- Trails and Trade Routes 1 (Box 121)
- Trails and Trade Routes 2 (Box 121)
- Trails and Trade Routes - Newspaper Articles, etc. (Box 121)
- Transportation (Box 121)
- Transportation - Modem (Box 121)
- Transportation - Primitive (Box 121)
- Travel - Visiting Indian Locations (Box 121)
- Treaties (Box 121)
- Tree Rings - Dendrochronolgy (Box 122)
- Tribal Claims Against the United States (Box 132)
- Tribal Courts (Box 122)
- Tribal Government (Box 122)
- Tribal Leaders (Box 122)
- Tribal Seals & Flags (Box 122)
- Trinidad and Tobago (Box 122)
- Trust funds (Box 122)
- Tsattine Indians (Box 122)
- Tsimshian Indians (Box 122)
- Tukuna Indians (Box 122)
- Tule River Indians (Box 122)
- Tunica Indians (Box 122)
- Tupi - Guarani Indians (Box 122)
- Turquoise (Box 122)
- Turtle Talk (Box 122)
- Tuscarora Indians (Box 122)
- Tushkahomman (Box 122)
- Tutelo Indians (Box 122)
- Twana Indians (Box 122)
- Tzotzil Indians (Box 122)
- Umpqua Indians (Box 122)
- Upper Skagit (Box 122)
- Urban Indian Centers (Box 122)
- Urbanization (Box 122)
- Uruguay (Box 122)
- Uruguay - Antiquities (Box 122)
- Uruguay - Indians (Box 122)
- Utah (Box 122)
- Utah - Antiquities 1 (Box 122)
- Utah - Antiquities 2 (Box 122)
- Utah - History (Box 123)
- Utah - Indians (Box 123)
- Ute Indians (Box 123)
- Ute Indians - Ethnology (Box 123)
- Ute Indians - Legal Articles (Box 123)
- Venezuela (Box 123)
- Venezuela - Antiquities 1 (Box 123)
- Venezuela - Antiquities 2 (Box 123)
- Venezuela - History (Box 123)
- Venezuela - Indians 1 (Box 123)
- Venezuela - Indians 2 (Box 123)
- Vermont (Box 123)
- Vermont - Antiquities (Box 123)
- Vermont - History (Box 123)
- Vermont - Indians (Box 124)
- Virgin Islands - History (Box 124)
- Virginia (Box 124)
- Virginia - Antiquities (Box 124)
- Virginia - Bibliography (Box 124)
- Virginia - History (Box 124)
- Virginia - Indians 1 (Box 124)
- Virginia - Indians 2 (Box 124)
- Walapai Indians (Box 124)
- Wampanoag Indians (Box 124)
- Wampum (Box 124)
- Wampum Articles & Corres. (Box 124)
- Wampum Belts (Box 124)
- Waorani Indians (Box 124)
- Wappo Indians (Box 124)
- War Service - World War I (Box 124)
- War Service - World War II (Box 124)
- Warao Idnians (Box 124)
- Warfare (Box 125)
- Wars 1 (Box 125)
- Wars 2 (Box 125)
- Wars 3 (Box 125)
- Wars - Blackhawk (Box 125)
- Wars - French & Indian War (Box 125)
- Wasco Confederation (Box 125)
- Washington D.C. Indians (Box 125)
- Washington State - Antiquities (Box 125)
- Washington State - History (Box 125)
- Washington State - Indians 1 (Box 125)
- Washington State - Indians 2 (Box 125)
- Washo Indians (Box 125)
- Water projects (Box 125)
- Water rights (Box 125)
- Watercraft - Canoes, Kayaks (Box 126)
- Weaving and textiles 1 (Box 126)
- Weaving and textiles 2 (Box 126)
- Weaving and textiles - Oversize (Box 131)
- Weaving and textiles - North America (Box 126)
- Weaving and textiles - Peru (Box 126)
- Weaving and textiles - South America (Box 126)
- Weaving and textiles - Southwest (Box 126)
- Websites (Box 126)
- Weddings (Box 126)
- West Indians (Box 126)
- West Indies (Box 126)
- West Indies - Antilles 1 (Box 126)
- West Indies - Antilles 2 (Box 126)
- West Indies - Antiquities 1 (Box 126)
- West Indies - Antiquities 2 (Box 127)
- West Indies - History (Box 127)
- West Indies - Indians (Box 127)
- West Indies - Lesser Antilles 1 (Box 127)
- West Indies - Lesser Antilles 2 (Box 127)
- West Virginia (Box 127)
- West Virginia - Antiquities (Box 127)
- West Virginia - History (Box 127)
- White House - Pre Conference (Box 127)
- Wichita Indians (Box 127)
- Wicocomoco Indians (Box 127)
- Winnebago Indians (Box 127)
- Wintun Indians (Box 127)
- Wintun Indians - Legislation (Box 127)
- Wisconsin (Box 127)
- Wisconsin - Antiquities 1 (Box 127)
- Wisconsin - Antiquities 2 (Box 127)
- Wisconsin - History (Box 128)
- Wisconsin - Indians (Box 128)
- Witoto Indians (Box 128)
- Wiyat Indians (Box 128)
- Women (Box 128)
- Wounded Knee 1 (Box 128)
- Wounded Knee 2 (Box 128)
- Writers (Box 128)
- Wyandot Indians (Box 128)
- Wyandot Indians - Legal documents (Box 128)
- Wyoming Indians (Box 128)
- Wyoming Indians - Antiquities (Box 128)
- Wyoming Indians - History (Box 128)
- Xicaque Indians (Box 128)
- Xinca Indians (Box 128)
- Yahgans (Box 128)
- Yakima Indians (Box 128)
- Yana Indians (Box 128)
- Yankton Indians (Box 128)
- Yanomamo Indians (Box 128)
- Yaqui Indians (Box 128)
- Yaqui Indians - Legal documents (Box 128)
- Yavapai Indians (Box 128)
- Yokuts Indians (Box 128)
- Yucatec Indians (Box 128)
- Yukian Indians (Box 129)
- Yuma Indians (Box 129)
- Yuman Indians (Box 129)
- Yuman Speaking Indians (Box 129)
- Yurok Indians (see also Hoopa Indian) (Box 129)
- Yurucari Indians (Box 129)
- Zapotec Indians (Box 129)
- Zuni Indians (Box 129)
- Zuni Indians - Antiquities (Box 129)
- Zuni Indians - Articles & Corres. (Box 129)
- Zuni Indians - Census (1941) Legal (Box 129)
- Zuni Indians - Ceremonies, songs, dances (Box 129)
- Zuni Indians - Ethnology (Box 129)
- Zuni Indians - Religion (Box 129)